'use strict'
const questionsBank = [
{
question: 'Which Pokémon has electricity-storing pouches on its cheeks?',
option1: 'Eevee',
option2: 'Ditto',
option3: 'Pikachu',
option4: 'Charmander',
answer: 3 
},

{
  question: 'How many Dragon Balls are there?',
  option1: 'Seven',
  option2: 'Five',
  option3: 'Ten',
  option4: 'Three',
  answer: 1 
  },

  {
    question: 'Which anime series revolves around a boy who sells his soul to a demon?',
    option1: 'Naruto',
    option2: 'Black Butler',
    option3: 'Bleach',
    option4: 'Attack on Titan',
    answer: 2 
    },

    {
      question: 'Whose body gained the properties of rubber after unintentionally eating a Devil Fruit?',
      option1: 'Kurosaki Ichigo',
      option2: 'Nami',
      option3: 'Saitama',
      option4: 'Monkey D. Luffy',
      answer: 4 
      },

      {
        question: 'Who protects the Silver Crystal?',
        option1: 'Levi Ackerman',
        option2: 'Satoru Gojo',
        option3: 'Sailor Moon',
        option4: 'Gon Freecss',
        answer: 4 
        },

        {
          question: 'Which anime series revolves around the Elric brothers?',
          option1: 'Naruto',
          option2: 'Fullmetal Alchemist',
          option3: 'Berserk',
          option4: 'Vinland Saga',
          answer: 2
          },

          {
            question: 'An outcast prince takes over the revolution by controlling the mind of others. Who is he?',
            option1: 'Lelouch Lanperouge',
            option2: 'Ikari Shinji',
            option3: 'Uchiha Itachi',
            option4: 'Hisoka',
            answer: 1 
            },

            {
              question: `In the anime ‘Hunter X Hunter’, which family is famous for being assassins?`,
              option1: 'Family of Kamado Tanjiro',
              option2: 'Family of Uchiha Sasuke ',
              option3: 'Family of Killua Zoldyck',
              option4: 'Family of Edward Elric',
              answer: 3 
              },

              {
                question: `Who was the first member of the First Levi Squad to die in ‘Attack on Titan’?`,
                option1: 'Historia Reiss',
                option2: 'Mikasa Ackerman',
                option3: 'Petra Rall',
                option4: 'Gunther Schultz',
                answer: 4 
                },

                {
                  question: `Who was the creator of the heart-touching movie ‘Spirited Away’ (2001)?`,
                  option1: 'Shinkai Makoto',
                  option2: 'Miyazaki Hayao',
                  option3: 'Nakamura Yutaka',
                  option4: 'Anno Hideaki',
                  answer: 2 
                  },

                  {
                    question: `What is the greatest taboo for the alchemists in ‘Fullmetal Alchemist’?`,
                    option1: 'Human transmutation',
                    option2: 'Killing',
                    option3: 'Transformation',
                    option4: 'Healing',
                    answer: 1 
                    },

                    {
                      question: `In Noragami, Yato was the god of _____`,
                      option1: 'Love and friendship',
                      option2: 'Prosperity',
                      option3: 'Calamity/war',
                      option4: 'Death',
                      answer: 3 
                      },



]